

Contact

ADDRESS

Bangkok, Thailand

PHONE

+66 (0) 80 900 8396

EMAIL

nuttha.cs@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://beamelet.github.io

Tech Skills

LANGUAGES

Python, R, Java, C#, Shell, SQL

WEB TECHNOLOGIES

React, Gatsby, Node.js

DATA FRAMEWORKS

Hadoop Ecosystem (Spark/Hive)

DATABASES

Microsoft SQL, Oracle, Teradata

CLOUD PLATFORMS

Amazon AWS, Google Cloud Platform, Microsoft Azure

VISUALISATION TOOLS

Tableau, Microsoft PowerBI

Highlights

TECH/ART CLUB (PRESENT)

Create digital art by combining creativity and technologies

TECH EVENTS (2014 – 2017)

ACM, IEEEXtream, NSC, DTAC Accelerate

PROGRAMMING CLUB (2013 – 2016)

Founded the club, held knowledge sharing, and participated in contests

MU BRAND AMBASSADOR (2013)

Represented Mahidol University in social services

About me

Having both consulting and engineering experience, I am a data-oriented individual who identifies problems and proposes solutions for customers and businesses. My goal is to make use of data to understand the complexity of our world and improve the quality of life on the planet.

Experience

DATA AND BUSINESS INTEGRATION ANALYST, ACCENTURE - 2018 - PRESENT

- Gathered and analysed requirements from banking product owners
- Designed and developed a classifier to classify bank customers
- Implemented data pipelines (ETL) for data integration and analytics
- Set up internal Git version control and guidelines for projects
- Designed and built a role-based access control on database system

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, MICROSOFT – 2016 - 2017

- Developed a content tool and services for documentation writers on docs.microsoft.com
- Visualised and analysed users' telemetry data
- Authored use cases and test plans

RESEARCH INTERN, BREMEN UNIVERSITY, GERMANY - 2015

• Improved data quality on OpenStreetMap by building an associative classifier to suggest types of green entities (e.g. park, garden, forest, etc.) to map contributors

Projects

TOPIC MODELLING OF CUSTOMER REVIEWS; MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY, TH - 2018 - 2019

• Processed and summarised text reviews (Natural Language Processing) from tourist attractions into topics, visualising customers' insights

NET CONTRIBUTION PREDICTION; AGODA, TH - 2018

• Predicted future revenue to support marketing investment decision making by developing linear regression model on customer history data

SAMSUNG GALAXY GIFT DASHBOARD; BUZZEBEES, TH - 2017

• Visualised user profiles and behaviours inside Samsung's application

HOME AUTOMATION FOR PHYSICALLY-IMPAIRED; MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY, TH - 2016

• Developed home automation controlled via brainwaves through Brain Computer Interface (BCI)

MOBILE APPLICATION FOR KIDS VISITING THE ZOO; MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY, TH – 2014

• Developed a mobile application which navigates and promotes wildlife conservation inside the zoo using augmented reality (AR)

Education

MASTER OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE; MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY, TH - 2019

• Researched on Statistical Modelling and Natural Language Processing

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY, TH – 2016

- Earned First Class Honours and Full Scholarships
- Assisted teaching on the course Data Structure and Algorithm Analysis
- Founded a programming club and participated in contests